Guide to the Jaime Davidovich Collection MSS.155
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Jaime Davidovich Art Files
  - Subseries D: Exhibition Catalogs, Publicity, and Press
    - Program, "Exposicion Jaime Davidovich, Pinturas y Dibujos" at Museu Nacional de Belas Artes, Rio de Janeiro., 1958 (Box 3, Folder 202)
    - Program, Davidovich exhibit at la Biblioteca Bernardino Rivadavia, Buenos Aires., 1961 (Box 3, Folder 203)
    - Program, "Jaime Davidovich and Delia Puzzovio Pinturas de 16 Al 31 de Mayo de 1962" at Nueva-Galeria de arte, Buenos Aires, Argentina. (Box 3, Folder 204)
    - Exhibition program, "Premio de Honor Ver y Estimar" at the Museo Nacional de Bellas Artes. Includes a Jaime Davidovich painting., 1962 (Box 5, Folder 205)
    - Davidovich show of paintings at the Canton Art Institute. Press and program., 1963 (Box 5, Folder 206)
    - Drake University Iberamerican Celebration program., 1971 (Box 5, Folder 207)
    - John Carroll, University, "Carroll Wall Project" program and photocopies., 1971 (Box 5, Folder 208)
    - Carroll Wall Project press, Fine Arts v. 18 n. 867. Original issue and photocopy of article., 1971 (Box 5, Folder 209)
    - Carroll Wall Project press, photocopy of "Art and Artists" column from Cleveland's The Plain Dealer., 1971 (Box 5, Folder 210)
    - Lake Erie Wall Project, program, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 211)
    - May Show at the Cleveland Museum of Art, press., 1971 (Box 5, Folder 212)
    - Akron Art Institute, Regional Invitational Exhibitions, press., 1972 (Box 5, Folder 213)
    - American Civil Liberties Union Benefit II, programs, publicity, and press., 1972 (Box 5, Folder 214)
    - Cleveland Museum of Art and The New Gallery. "The Sidewalk Project" publicity., 1972 (Box 5, Folder 215)
    - Master Drawings and Works on Paper at the New Gallery in Cleveland, announcement., 1972 (Box 5, Folder 216)
    - Lake Erie College Microfoam Tape Proejct, publicity., 1972 (Box 5, Folder 217)
    - Six Artists Show at Akron Art Institute, catalog., 1972 (Box 5, Folder 218)
    - Bykert Gallery, exhibit announcement., 1973 (Box 5, Folder 219)
    - Rail Bridge Project press, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 220)
    - 6 Shows, exhibition at New Gallery, publicity materials., 1973 (Box 5, Folder 221)
    - Whitney Biennial Catalog, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 222)
    - Whitney Biennial press, "Indeed an Honor" in Plain Dealer about Jaime Davidovich meeting Salvador Dali., 1973 (Box 5, Folder 223)
    - Institute of Contemporary Arts and Communication (ICA and CAYC), London. Press and Publicity., 1974 (Box 5, Folder 224)
    - Art Today USA catalog, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 225)
    - 3 Mercer Store, advertisements and press reviews.l, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 227)
    - Anthology Film Archives, Video Showw by Jaime Davidovich, publicity and press release., 1976 (Box 5, Folder 228)
    - "Baseboard" screening at The Kitchen, description, promotional stills, and press release., 1976 (Box 5, Folder 229)
    - New American Filmmaker series at the Whitney, press release., 1976 (Box 5, Folder 231)
    - New American Filmmaker series at the Whitney, artist bios., 1976 (Box 5, Folder 232)
    - New American Filmmaker series at the Whitney, press., 1976 (Box 5, Folder 233)
    - Technological Art Invitational exhibition at Towson State College Art Gallery, catalog., 1976 (Box 5, Folder 234)
    - Video VII screening at the Museum of Modern Art, publicity postcard., 1976 (Box 5, Folder 235)
    - Everson Museum of Art in Syracuse NY, Jaime Davidovich Show. Materials include publicity and programs., 1977 (Box 5, Folder 236)
    - University of Iowa, installation and lecture at Corroboree Gallery. Materials include publicity postcards, fliers, and press., 1979 (Box 5, Folder 237)
    - "TV finds its place among fine Arts" in The Plain Dealer, about Jaime Davidovich and Qube project, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 238)
    - Video screening in Holland, press., 1980 (Box 5, Folder 239)
    - Mudd Video 4, four hour marathon screening, press., 1981 (Box 5, Folder 240)
    - Alternatives in Retrosepct, an Historical Overview at the New Museum. Jaime Davidovich's collaboration with Stuart Sherman appears as part of 3 Mercer St. catalog and press release., 1981 (Box 5, Folder 241)
    - Athens Internation Film and Video Festival catalog, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 242)
    - International Media Meeting Catalog, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 243)
    - World Wide Video Festival, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 244)
    - "Fandangos" magazine, advertisement to order an International Media Meeting catalog, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 245)
    - International Impact Art Festival, Kyoto Municipal Museum of Art, Seoul National Museum of Art, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 246)
    - Watching Television, a video event at the Universityy of Illinois at Urbana-Champaign, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 247)
    - Bienal de la Habana, catalog, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 249)
    - Bienal de la Habana, catalog apendice, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 250)
    - Cleveland Revisited exhibition featuring April Gornik, Jaime Davidovich, Michael Vessa, cataloges and publicity mailing., 1984 (Box 5, Folder 251)
    - "Evita" press, 1984-1991 (Box 5, Folder 252)
    - Video: A Retrospective 1974-1984 at Long Beach Museum of Art, catalog and program (Box 5, Folder 253)
    - Global Village National Documentary Tour, includes "Evita". Press release, publicity, and catalog., 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 254)
    - Collected reviews about Jaime Davidovich, grouped together by artist., 1985-1991 (Box 5, Folder 255)
    - Televisions Impact on Contemporary Art at The Queens Museum, catalog., 1986 (Box 5, Folder 256)
    - Unconventional Constitutional Convention, press and publicity., 1986 (Box 5, Folder 257)
    - Transculture Transmedia at Exit Art. Includes "Evita", exhibition announcement, press release, program schedule., 1986 (Box 5, Folder 259)
    - The Latin American Spirit, Art and Artists in the United States, 1920-1970 T Bronx Museum of the Arts. Press pack., 1988 (Box 5, Folder 260)
    - Diane Brown Gallery, Jaime Davidovich showing. Exhibition catalog and announcement., 1988 (Box 5, Folder 262)
    - The Debt exhibit at Exit Art, promotional mailing., 1988 (Box 5, Folder 263)
    - The Debt exhibit, press release, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 264)
    - Museo del Barrio, National Latino Film and Video Festival, program., 1988 (Box 5, Folder 265)
    - Pervasive Symbiosis, Ten Argentine-New York Artists at Carla Stellweg. Publicity mateirals and press release., 1989 (Box 5, Folder 266)
    - Stationary Show, Wooster Enterprises 1977-1978. Program, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 267)
    - "Contexto Transcultural" at ICI, screening of Jaime Davidovich work, promotional card., 1990 (Box 5, Folder 269)
    - ICI, press, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 270)
    - ICI, videoteca forms., 1990 (Box 5, Folder 271)
    - The Charade of Mastery at the Whitney Museum, Downtown. Programs and Invites., 1990 (Box 5, Folder 272)
    - The Decade Show, programs, publicity and press, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 273)
    - Video Art Internacional at the Museo de Bellas Artes, Argentina, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 274)
    - "Forces/Farces" at Exit Art, publicity announcements., 1991 (Box 5, Folder 275)
    - "Forces/Fraces" at Exit Art, exhibit handout, program notes and artist resume., 1991 (Box 5, Folder 276)
    - "Forces/Farces" at Exit Art, press release, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 277)
    - Forces/Farces at Exit Art, press, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 278)
    - "Los pueblos quieren saber de que se trata" video installation at Fundacion Banco Patricios. Publicity announcement., 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 279)
    - "Los pueblos queiren saber de que se trata" at Fundacion Banco Patricios, Artist Bio, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 280)
    - "Lo Falso, Lo Virtual, Lo Real" exhibition at ICI, press review., 1994 (Box 5, Folder 283)
    - "Lo Falso, Lo Virtual, Lo Real" exhibition at ICI, additional press., 1994 (Box 5, Folder 284)
    - "Scars, Pleasure, Sacrifice" exhibit at Colombian Center, NYC. A collaboration between the Permanent Mission of Colombia to the UN and the Consulate General of Argentina. Exhibition catalog., 1994 (Box 5, Folder 285)
    - "Scars, Pleasure, Sacrifice" exhibit at Colombian Center, New York City. Promotional materials and programs., 1994 (Box 5, Folder 286)
    - "La Tierra Prometida" at ICI Buenos Aires, exhibit publicity., 1995 (Box 5, Folder 287)
    - "La Tierra Prometida" at ICI Buenos Aires, press review., 1995 (Box 5, Folder 289)
    - "La Tierra Prometida" at ICI Buenos Aires. Additional press., 1995 (Box 5, Folder 290)
    - El Museo del Barrio 25th Anniversary Exhibition. Publicity postcards and exhibition synopsis., 1995 (Box 5, Folder 291)
    - First exhibition of Euro-American video art, in Buenos Aires. November 11 -17, 1996. Program (Box 5, Folder 293)
    - Festival Internacional de video y Artes Electronicas (FIV) in Buenos Aires, Argentina; program, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 294)
    - FIV press, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 295)
    - "Legacy/Legado" exhibition at the Old State House in Hartford, CT; publicity announcements., 1996 (Box 5, Folder 296)
    - "Legacy/Legado" exhibition, press., 1996 (Box 5, Folder 297)
    - Isis conceptual Laboratory "Looking for the Pieces" publicity, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 299)
    - 3rd exhibition of Euroamerican digital and video art in Buenos Aires, Argentina,program., 1998 (Box 5, Folder 300)
    - Zocalo (1975-1998) exhibition at the Museo de Arte Moderno in Buenos Aires. Publicity brochure, invitation, and contact sheet. (Box 6, Folder 302)
    - University of Iowa, show curated over the internet. Essay and Daviovich work downloaded from the University of Iowa website 31 January 1999. (Box 6, Folder 303)
    - Anthology Film Archives, screening of Davidovich video art works, "Interior" and "Two Windows" Publicity flier and press release., undated (Box 6, Folder 305)
    - Colaborative Latino/Latino Collaborative. Brochure features Jaime Davidovich's work., undated (Box 6, Folder 306)
    - The Kitchen, "Baseboard" screening, publicity postcard., undated (Box 6, Folder 307)
    - Long Beach Museum of Art, "Shared Realities, A Cultural Arts cable series". Publicity and programmining information, undated (Box 6, Folder 308)
    - La Television Interactivity, screening event in honor of Jaime Davidovich sponsored by Taller, Imagen, y Sonido in Buenos Aires, Argentina; press release., undated (Box 6, Folder 309)
  - Subseries E: Correspondence
    - Akron Art Institute, correspondence regarding the Regional Invitational, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 310)
    - Alonso, Rodrigo. Professor at the University of Buenos Aires., 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 311)
    - Alonso, Rodrigo. Correspondence regarding "Zocalo" exhibition., 1998 (Box 6, Folder 312)
    - American Civil Liberties Union Benefit II, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 313)
    - Arts Cable Exchange Conference in Minneapolis, Correspondence, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 314)
    - Basso, Carlota Alvarez of theReina Sofia Museo Nacional Centro de Arte., 1999 (Box 6, Folder 315)
    - Buccellato, Laura of the Museo de Arte Moderno in Buenos Aires., undated (Box 6, Folder 316)
    - Bykert Gallery, correspondence regarding the Ceiling Project., 1973 (Box 6, Folder 317)
    - Cal Arts, correspondence regarding the visiting artist program, 1991-1993 (Box 6, Folder 318)
    - Camitzer, Luis., 1998 (Box 6, Folder 319)
    - Chong, Celia of Global Village video and television documentary festival, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 320)
    - Contemporary Arts Center, Cincinnati, Ohio., undated (Box 6, Folder 321)
    - Clerk, Pierre of the SoHo Community Council, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 322)
    - Cuperman, Lila, undated (Box 6, Folder 323)
    - The Decade Show, sponsored by the Museum of Contemporary Hispanic Art, The New Museum, The Studio Museum in Harlem., 1990 (Box 6, Folder 324)
    - Edwards, Susan. Curator of the Hunter College Galleries., 1995 (Box 6, Folder 325)
    - Esperanto Internet Services, LLC correspondence regarding the Legacy/Legado exhibit at the Connecticut State House., 1996 (Box 6, Folder 326)
    - correspondence regarding the Euclid Avenue Bridge., 1993 (Box 6, Folder 327)
    - Everson Museum, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 328)
    - Exit Art, correspondence regarding "The End", 2000 (Box 6, Folder 329)
    - Friedman, Martin of the Walker Art Center., 1982 (Box 6, Folder 330)
    - Fundacion Antorchas, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 331)
    - Fundacion Patricios, 1991-1992 (Box 6, Folder 332)
    - Gagnon, Jean of the National Gallery in Ontario Canada., 1996 (Box 6, Folder 333)
    - Galloway, David. Correspondence regarding Loraine College and Art Today: Tehran., 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 334)
    - Glusberg, Jorge., 1994-1997 (Box 6, Folder 335)
    - Godoy, Lilian of the Bienal de la Habana., 1984 (Box 6, Folder 336)
    - Hall, David, undated (Box 6, Folder 337)
    - Handy, Ellen of the International Center of Photography, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 338)
    - Heitt, Janet regarding translation and proof reading., 1998 (Box 6, Folder 339)
    - Heiss, Alanna of P.S.1 Contemporary Art Center., 1997 (Box 6, Folder 340)
    - Helft, Jorge., 1990 (Box 6, Folder 341)
    - Helft, Marion., 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 342)
    - Henning, Edward of the Cleveland Museum of Art., 1973 (Box 6, Folder 343)
    - Ingberman, Jeanette of Exit Art regarding "debt" exhibition., 1988 (Box 6, Folder 344)
    - Instituto de Cooperacion Iberoamericana and Centro de Arte y Comunicacion correspondence regarding exhibit in Brussels, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 345)
    - Instituto de Cooperacion Iberoamericana., 1990 (Box 6, Folder 346)
    - Instituto de Cooperacion Iberoamericana regarding "Lo Falso, Lo Virtual, Lo Real" exhibit., 1994 (Box 6, Folder 347)
    - Instituto de Cooperacion Iberoamericana regarding "Ver y Estimar"., 1994 (Box 6, Folder 348)
    - Instituto de Cooperacion Iberoamericana regarding"La Tierra Prometida", 1995 (Box 6, Folder 349)
    - Isis conceptual laboratory regarding "Looking for the Pieces", 1997 (Box 6, Folder 350)
    - Jackie., 1971 (Box 6, Folder 351)
    - Jeanjean, Stephanie of Le Consortium in Dijon France., 1997 (Box 6, Folder 352)
    - John., undated (Box 6, Folder 353)
    - Jones, Philip Mallory of the Ithaca Video Festival., 1976 (Box 6, Folder 354)
    - Kite, Laddy. Jaime Davidovich inquiring about a Visual Studies Workshop., undated (Box 6, Folder 355)
    - Krause, H.B. Jaime Davidovich to Krause at Syracuse University., 1997 (Box 6, Folder 356)
    - LaFerla, Jorge., 1995-1997 (Box 6, Folder 357)
    - Lassallette, Carlos regarding"Recordando el Futuro", 1994 (Box 6, Folder 358)
    - Leavitt, Thomas regarding H.Johnson Museum., 1979 (Box 6, Folder 359)
    - Lippard, Lucy., 1971 (Box 6, Folder 360)
    - Loeffler, Carl of ArtCom, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 361)
    - Mack, Daniel regarding EAT show at Lake Erie, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 362)
    - MIT Press regarding "Open Circuits", 1974 (Box 6, Folder 363)
    - Mediapolis., 1997 (Box 6, Folder 364)
    - Museo del Barrio regarding "Artists Talk Back, Visual Conversations with El Museo", 1995 (Box 6, Folder 365)
    - Museo del Barrio, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 366)
    - Museo Nacional d Bellas Artes, Buenos Aires regarding an archive of video art and experimental film., 1998 (Box 6, Folder 367)
    - Museum of Modern Art, New York regarding Davidovich's 1999 donation., 1999-2000 (Box 6, Folder 368)
    - NBC regarding Late Night with David Letterman., 1982 (Box 6, Folder 369)
    - New Museum, regarding Celebration III, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 370)
    - Ohio State University., 1974 (Box 6, Folder 371)
    - Point of Contact., 1994 (Box 6, Folder 372)
    - Puzzovio, Delila. Part 1 of 2, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 373)
    - Puzzovio, Delila. Part 2 of 2, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 374)
    - Puzzovio, Delila. Part 1 of 2, undated (Box 6, Folder 375)
    - Puzzovio, Dlilia, Part 2 of 2., undated (Box 6, Folder 376)
    - Rabinovich, Raquel. Letter of recommendation by Jaime Davidovich., 1999 (Box 6, Folder 377)
    - Ramirez, Mari Carmen., 1998 (Box 6, Folder 378)
    - Rappaport, Herman., undated (Box 6, Folder 379)
    - Rodriguez, Geno of the Alternative Museum., 1995 (Box 6, Folder 380)
    - Sanjines, Jose regarding Jaime Davidovich's Borges work for Point of Contact., undated (Box 6, Folder 381)
    - Seltzer, Phyllis regarding EAT Exhibit at Lake Erie., 1972 (Box 6, Folder 382)
    - Sharp, Willoughby, undated (Box 6, Folder 383)
    - Simpson, Charles regarding "SoHo So What" interview, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 384)
    - Slavin, Sara of the John Weber Gallery. Correspondence regarding Buenos Aires exhibition., 1973 (Box 6, Folder 385)
    - Solway Gallery and Dayton Art Institute regarding the All-Ohio Invitational, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 386)
    - Solway, Carl regarding "Not In New York" gallery show., 1974 (Box 6, Folder 387)
    - State Office Building project, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 388)
    - Stoney, George, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 389)
    - Suarez, Sandra Antelo. Jaime Davidovich letter regarding Diaspora website., 1996 (Box 6, Folder 390)
    - Synapse Video Center, undated (Box 6, Folder 391)
    - Troncoso, Joe of CalArts, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 392)
    - United States Information Agency (USIA), 1998 (Box 6, Folder 393)
    - University of Iowa, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 394)
    - University of Iowa, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 395)
    - University of Iowa regarding visiting scholars program., 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 396)
    - Univeristy of Iowa, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 397)
    - Varrian, John of Finch College Museum of Art regarding Jaime Davidovich's gift of "Draped Tape Project", 1973 (Box 6, Folder 398)
    - Video Cuba, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 399)
    - Video Culture Symposium, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 400)
    - Whitney Biennial, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 401)
    - Whitney Museum, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 402)
    - Whitney Museum, Downtown regarding video program, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 403)
    - Wong, Ernest of Angel Art '93 regarding "Remember the Past", 1993 (Box 6, Folder 404)
    - Printing bids for Diane Brown Gallery Catalogue, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 405)
    - Correspondence regarding arranging an retrospective of Jaime Davidovich's work, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 406)
    - Letters of introduction from Jaime Davidovich to museum curators., 1998 (Box 6, Folder 407)
  - Subseries F: Publication of Jaime Davidovich's Work
    - "Video Art Out to Lunch"Jaime Davidovich interviews Les Brown, ArtCome v. 6 n.2, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 408)
    - Real Life Magazine #16, "Context-Come Together Textere-To weave" by Jaime Davidovich., 1986 (Box 6, Folder 409)
    - Photocopies of Manifestos written by Jaime Davidovich, published in multiple sources., 1986-1987 (Box 6, Folder 410)
    - Photocopies of assorted published works., 1986-1991 (Box 6, Folder 411)
    - "Poster-Chicago Editing Center 1982" folder includes pubications of Jaime Davidovich's storyboards including one with TeeVee. Also a discussion of Jaime Davidovich's Qube projecct. (Box 6, Folder 411A)
    - Real Life Magazine, invitation to create a piece for publication in the magazine and the artist's production materials including photographs, notes, and negatives., 1989 (Box 6, Folder 412)
    - "Self Potrait by Jaime Davidovich" in the New Yorker [page 13], 1991 (Box 6, Folder 413)
    - Point of Contact, v.4 n,2 includes work "A Video Promenade with Jorge Louis Borges" by Jaime Davidovich, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 414)
    - Arte Audiovisual: Tecnologias y discursos. Conceptulized and compiled by Jore La Ferla. "Marketing hoareno de videoarte" by Jaime Davidovich., 1998 (Box 7, Folder 416)
    - photocopies of Avalanche Advertisement, " Jaime Davidovich, Available for Projects Anywhere in the World"., undated (Box 7, Folder 417)
    - photocopy of ArtCom article by Jaime Davidovich about the future of art., undated (Box 7, Folder 418)
  - Subseries G: Publications Designed or Printed by Jaime Davidovich
    - Cleveland Museum "Taped Sidewalk" flier design, production materials., 1972 (Box 7, Folder 420)
    - Video VII at MoMA, publicity flier mock up, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 422)
    - "Baseboard" screening at the Kitchen, publicity flier mock up, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 423)
    - From Cover to Uncover catalog, content and design by Jaime Davidovich, printed by Wooster Enterprises., 1977 (Box 7, Folder 424)
    - "All in the TV Family" postcard by Jaime Davidovich, printed by Wooster Enterprises., 1982 (Box 7, Folder 426)
    - Diane Brown Gallery Catalog, negatives, contact sheets, and prints., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 427)
    - Diane Brown Gallery Catalog, essay by Susan Morgan, "Theme Music for Jaime Davidovich", 1988 (Box 7, Folder 428)
    - Diane Brown Gallery Catalog, annotated draft., 1988 (Box 7, Folder 429)
    - Diane Brown Gallery Catalog, notes, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 430)
    - Diane Brown Gallery Catalog, page proofs, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 431)
    - Diane Brown Gallery Catalog, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 432)
    - photocopy of the Diane brown Gallery Catalog, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 433)
    - Anthology Film Archive letterhead, undated (Box 7, Folder 434)
    - Letterhead including "Watching the World" and "Live! Show", undated (Box 7, Folder 436)
    - Book design, notes., undated (Box 7, Folder 437)
    - Flux Stationery by George Maciunas, mock ups for Wooster Enterprises printing., undated (Box 7, Folder 438)
    - Pozo, la Bienal de Venecia. Booklet produced by Davidovich, Cubero, Renzo, Link, Mercanti, and Noain (Box 7, Folder 440)
  - Subseries H: Teaching and Presentations
    - Instituteo Torcuato Di Tella, The First two and a half years. Davidovich was the representative to the United States for the Art Center of the DiTella Foundation in Buenos Aires, Argentina n 1965., 1960-1962 (Box 7, Folder 441)
    - Photographs of Jaime Davidovich teaching at the School of Visual Arts, Bahia Blanca., 1962 (Box 7, Folder 442)
    - Art education for International Understanding in Montreal. Jaime Davidovich participated in a panel about Art Education and Mass Communication. Black and white photographs and program., 1963 (Box 7, Folder 443)
    - Chicago Editing Center, "Wake Up" presentation notes., 1974 (Box 7, Folder 445)
    - International Video Art Symposium at Agnes Etherington Art Center, Kingston Ontario, Canada. Transcript, bulletin., 1977 (Box 7, Folder 446)
    - Arts Cable Exchange Conference in Minneapolis. Programming and registration materials., 1981 (Box 7, Folder 447)
    - Perspectives on the Avant-Garde at University of Iowa. Publicity materials, notes, script, contact infomration, black and white negatives and photographs., 1981 (Box 7, Folder 448)
    - The Artist and Television, teleconference at the University of Iowa., 1982 (Box 40, Folder 449)
    - "Video/Culture an International Audio-Video Festival" program information, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 450)
    - "Video/Culture" symposium promotional materials., 1983 (Box 40, Folder 451)
    - Video/Culture Symposium press, 1983 (Box 40, Folder 452)
    - University of Iowa community and department information, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 454)
    - Symposium: Video, Performance, Theory at University of Iowa. Announcement and Schedule., 1987 (Box 40, Folder 456)
    - Crossing Over: Video, Criticism, Theory symposium at University of Iowa. Publicity flier with schedule., 1988 (Box 40, Folder 457)
    - CalArts workshop Project, course description and campus maps., 1992 (Box 40, Folder 458)
    - University of Iowa visiting scholars program., 1993 (Box 40, Folder 459)
    - Monologue notes., 1998 (Box 40, Folder 460)
    - Syracuse International Film and Video Festival. Dossier., 2004 (Box 40, Folder 461)
    - "Home marketing of Video Art" by Jaime Davidovich., undated (Box 40, Folder 462)
    - "Art turns on TV" by Jaime Davidovich, undated (Box 40, Folder 463)
    - Notecards, "Escuela Bellas Artes", "MoMA", "Mesa Redonda". English and Spanish, grouped by Jaime Davidovich., undated (Box 40, Folder 464)
  - Subseries I: Photographs of Jaime Davidovich